George Brooks Additional Papers /4148
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- ILR 708 sp 78 Current, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- ILR 708 Spring 1977 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Industrial Relations in Hospital & Nursing & H., Industry, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- ILR 708 Sp 77 Administrative, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- ILR 708 Sp 77 Reserve lists, etc., 1977 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- ILR 708 Sp 77 Grades, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- ILR 708 Sp77 Evaluation, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- ILR 708 Sp 1977 Sessions (Box 19, Folder 13)
- ILR 708 Sp. 1977 Syllabus, etc. (Box 19, Folder 14)
- ILR 708 Sp. 77 Case Material (Orig.), 1977 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Case material comments, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Other distributions, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Possible Cases, 1975-1977 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- ILR 708 Sp 77 Examinations, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- ILR 708 Lectures notes, Outline, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Source Material, 1974-1976 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- ILR 708 - Spring 1976 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- ILR 708 - S '76 Administrative, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- ILR 708 1976 Grades (Box 19, Folder 24)
- ILR 708 1976 Case and other material (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Problems in Union Democracy, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- ILR 582 Sp 73 Syllabus, etc., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- ILR 582 Sp 73 Term Papers, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- ILR 582 Final Term Papers, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- ILR 582 Sp '73 Benson Seminar, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Students, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Lectures, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Biography, Photos, 1986-1989 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Newspaper comments, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Labor-manage-ment relations, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Arden House 1962-1976 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Cornell Exec. Dev. Program, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- (1965) Cornell Exec. Dev. Prog. 7/22/65 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Foreign Service Inst. (A-200), 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Foreign Service Inst. (A-407), 1963 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Other, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- IRA Finger Lakes 4-27-77, 5-12-76, 5-13-70, 1970-1977 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- General Electric 2-20-68, 9-24-68, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Midstate IRA Norwich 11/11/78, 5/23/89, 5/22/84, 4-23-85, 1978-1989 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Corning Glass 1-27-77, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- James River Follow-up, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Arrangements, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- James River Richmond 10/20/88, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- James River 10/27/88, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- James River Data, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- James River Expenses, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- James River Corp. 1989 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Other Programs (except Cornell), 1968-1971 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- L-M relations- specific subjects (Box 20, Folder 26)
- C/B and technological change, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- NICB (1-18-68), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- American Institute of Ind'l Engineers, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Assoc. Degree Program C/B & Productivity, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- World Bank: Tech Change & Transport Labor, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Elmira Rotary 2/14/67, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Government intervention, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Arbitration, 1963-1967 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Strikes, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Cornell Conference 12/7/65, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 36)
- Illinois - Trade Union Power and the Public interest, 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 37)
- Chamber of Commerce, Dayton 3-67, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 38)
- Williams College, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 39)
- Scott Paper 4/30/80, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 40)
- Industrial Management Clubs, 1968-1978 (Box 20, Folder 41)
- IMC Rochester 5-17-84, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 42)
- IMC Cortland 4-11-84, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 43)
- IMC Bradford County 11-9-83 (Box 20, Folder 44)
- IMC Finger Lakes 9/13/83, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 45)
- Labor 2000 10-1-84, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 46)
- Changes in Labor Move. 7-25-85 Labor Studies grad 6/89, 1985-1989 (Box 20, Folder 47)
- Organizing - Union Carbide 5/15/79, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 48)
- Cornell programs, 1966-1982 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Cornell Engineering 1/12/67, 1/16/69, 1/14/70, 1967-1970 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Golf Course Managers, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Ornamental Horticulturists 1/31/73, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Summer Course "Negotiations" 6/12/75, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Credit Union Conference 8/9/77, 8/10/82, 1977-1982 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- BPA Continuing Education 2/73, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- LMSA Compliance Officers 6/6-7/72 4/15-16/73 6/26-27/73, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Printing Industry 7/22-24/79, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Printing Industry 7/25/77, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Hotel School Syracuse China 6/22/86, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Personnel Administrators, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- CB Seminar July 1987, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- CB Seminar 6/89, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- ASPA South African Personnel Group, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Unions in Government, 1965-1971 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- AFSCME Staff 3/21-22/65, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- CSEA Staff 1/10-11,16-17/67, 4/20,27/67, 5/3/67, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- IRS 5-19-71 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Ind'l College of the Armed Forces 1/29/71, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Municipalities, countries, 1966-1976 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Hospitals (Cath Char. 5/4-5/66), 1966 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Home Econ. Dept. of Inst. Mg't., 1967-1969 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- St. Luke's 10/12/65, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- DC-MD-VA-Hospital Assn. 3/25/81, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Rehabilitation management, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Rehab Mgt. (Ron House) 4/9/76, 8/16/77, 5/12/78, 1976-1978 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Rehab Mgt. Chicago 11/8-9/78, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Program, arrangements, participants, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Material used 1978 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- GB Notes, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Agreements, other background mat'l, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Rehab Mgt. 5/1,2/79, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Rehab Mgt. May 14-16, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 34)
- NYSA Rehab Buffalo 9/9/85, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- NYSA Rehab 4-20-88, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Failure of C/B in Public Employment IMC Syracuse 12-14-71, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Schools, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- SUNY Administrators 10-17-72, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- LMRS/NASE summer program, 6/20-25/76, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- NASE 4/18/77 Arlington, Virginia, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Ithaca College AAUP 2-22-78, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- New Jersey School Boards Assoc. 8-8-78, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- State Conservation Dept. 4/9/69, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Correction Officers 11/8/82, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Urban League 1/12/66, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Cornell Summer Work Program, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Other, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Oxford May 1965 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Univ. of Michigan March 1966 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Hartford Mfgs. Ass'n. 6/16/66, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Ensign-Bickford 10/27/66, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Cornell - other (before 1961) (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Articles, 1948-1971 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- List of Publications, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- "Reflections of Unions", 1965 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Labor in the 80's New Politics, 1985-1991 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Atlantic Monthly July 1958 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- "The Sources of Vitality", 1978 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Saposs papers, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- "Relevance of Labor History" (IRRA 1961) (Box 22, Folder 27)
- "..in Twenty Years" (MIT), 1957 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- "A Case for Teachers Unions", 1964 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- "Rivalry among Teachers Organizations", 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Alliance for Labor Action, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Industrial relations, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Labor participation in government, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- A Half Century of Challenge, 1991-1993 (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Collective Bargaining, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- "Structure" McKinsey Seminar '60, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 36)
- "Security of Worker Institutions" MLR Jun. '63, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 37)
- Extra Copies, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 38)
- Need for rival unionism, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 39)
- Seniority in Southern Pulp, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 40)
- Norgren-Hill Study, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 41)
- Books Reviews, 1974-1993 (Box 22, Folder 42)
- Comments on manuscript, 1962-1992 (Box 22, Folder 43)
- Trade Union Monograph Series, 1964-1980 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Reviews for ILR Review, 1982-1991 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Reviews for Monthly Labor Review, 1961-1973 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Comparative Union Democracy, 1977-1986 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Other articles, etc. (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Monthly Labor Review, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Consultation, 1976-1980 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Corn Products Co., 1974-1979 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Discrimination Cases, 1957-1979 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- CCC Contract, 1965-1970 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- CCC Seniority Rosters, 1968-1972 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Miller vs. Continental Can, 1969-1979 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Training Meijer 1970 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Meijer and CIU 951, 1969-1974 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Special Notes, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- USA - GWB, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Strike 1975 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Board of Directors, 1972-1976 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- NAWCAS General, 1967-1981 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Ingersoll - Rand Program, 1969-1977 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Ithaca Gun - Directory, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Current, 1982-1991 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Other Consultation, 1975-1980 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Westvaco-PEWS 1987 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- De Laval, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Geissinger Medical Center, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Special Metals Corporation, 1980-1982 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Regents External Degree-Williams 1989 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Regents External Degree-Rifkin 1984 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Monsanto, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Monsanto Background material, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Monsanto Notes: meeting 9/22/76, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Consultation completed, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Dupont Corporation, 1964-1966 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- O-AT-KA Diary, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Distillers Chemicals and Plastics Limited, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Kennecott Copper Co., 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- Brunswick Corp., 1966 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- Consultation, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 39)
- Clever Hans, 1982-1984 (Box 23, Folder 40)
- Current, 1983-1992 (Box 23, Folder 41)
- Background, Discussion, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 42)
- Collective bargaining 1983 (Box 23, Folder 43)
- Collective bargaining, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 44)
- Agreement 1983 (Box 23, Folder 45)
- Strike, Etc., 1982 (Box 23, Folder 46)
- Current, 1984-1987 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Administrative, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Representation, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Bargaining 1983 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Bargaining 1982 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Bargaining, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Agreement, 1980-1985 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Tompkins County Hospital, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- RCA Mock Barg. 6-4-79, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Program Material, 1976-1979 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Nepera Chemical Fall 1979 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Off-Campus Instruction (Corning), 1982-1984 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- ILR 500 Sp 84 Collective Bargaining, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Course evaluations, corres., 1984 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Administration, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Sessions, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Syllabus and readings (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Material distributed, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Mock bargaining material, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Contact Administration, 1983-1985 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Administration, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Corning CCFL Spring 1989 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Public Programs, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Office of Employee Relns 3/12/84, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Case - Rockefeller Institute, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Department of Health, 1983-1988 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Program Development, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Facilitators, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Organization of Groups, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Training material, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- ABC Paper Co. case, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- GB original presentation, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Bibliography, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Evaluation (Box 24, Folder 34)
- NYSEG, 1984-1986 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- NYSEG workshop 4/1/87, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 36)
- NCR, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 37)
- Union Carbide, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 38)
- Administrative, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 39)
- Background Material, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 40)
- Negotiations 1981 (Box 24, Folder 41)
- Negotiations 1983 (Box 24, Folder 42)
- Reports and Findings, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 43)
- Meeting, Charleston 5/15-16/85, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 44)
- Agreement, etc., 1981-1983 (Box 24, Folder 45)
- Machinists Local 598, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 46)
- Interview notes, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 47)
- NLRB case 70, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Committee University as Employer, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Minutes, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- ACE Libraries, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Grievance Procedure - Related official policy, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Mattoon, June, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Union Activities, 1987-1992 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- COLA, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- CU Personnel matters, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Planning Committees, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Administration, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Agenda, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Comments on drafts from outside committee, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- GWB notes, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- GWB Copies, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Other than '70 report, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- The Voice, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Students, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Intern Spring 93, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Intern Spring 93 Michael Alpert, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Intern Spring '93 Jennifer Calhoun, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Glamstein, David Intern Spring 1993, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Marchant, Michael Intern Spring 1993, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Fall 1992 Interns (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Choudbury, Rudy Fall '92, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Fall ' 92 Schmelkin, Steven, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Spring 1992 Interns, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Almy, James Sp '92, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Belovin, Allyson Sp '92, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- JEW, Michael Spring '92, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- F '91 Hartnett, Jeff, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Interns Fall 1991 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Montouri, John Fall 1991 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Star, Charles Fall 1991 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Ulrich, Corey Fall 1991 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Young, Dan Fall '91, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Interns Former, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Beldner, Harvey Sp. 1991 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Bowers Elizabeth S. 87, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Bowling, Lance Fall 1990 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- De Traglia, Joseph Spring '91, 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Litten, Jordan Fall 1990 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Niles, Kara Fall '90, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- O'Brien, Kelly Fall '90, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Raymond, Cheryl Spring 1990, 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Seroussi, Ruth Fall 1990 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Stern, Steve Summer '91, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Wagner, Eric Spring 1991, 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Willig, Jennifer Fall 1990 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Moreland, David Fall '90, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Honors Theses, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Monterosso, Christine F '89, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- ILR 499, 1988-1991 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Kaufman, Jack ILR 499 Spring '92, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Bedell, Darren F '91, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Jacobstein, Douglas F '91, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Litten, Jordan F '91, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Meyer, Josh F '91, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Oronsky, Carl F '91, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Crawford, Joanne F' 90, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Special Students, 1988-1990 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Bernstein, Robert, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Hale, Andrea, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Handelman, Jeff Public Administration, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Pagnucco, Adam Masters Thesis, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Rochester, Andrew, 1988-1990 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Richard Shenkan, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Tacy, Mitchell, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- Job applicants and vacanies, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- Building Project, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- Golden Key Society, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 36)
- School Districts, 1967-1970 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- CWA Administration of CB agr't, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Training for post office staff 21, 16 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Training Chapter Chairmen (AFT), 1970 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- 5G performance, 1964-1972 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Training 1199 NYC, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Course 1970 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Canandaigua, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Nursing Home Consultants, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Development of Program, 1964-1965 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Productivity in Public Service, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Meat Cutters New Employees, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- (1969) (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Reed College, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Copy rights, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Conferences, Faculty, 1963-1965 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- AFSCME national, 1965-1968 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Transit Authority - NYC, 1968-1972 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Course Material 1970, 1968-1970 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- NY City Hospital, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Background research, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Course revisions, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Course material as of 10-68 (complete), 1968 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Hospital Manual, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- Representation (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Welfare Department, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- IAM-NY State, 1966-1970 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- Course Material, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- Course Material (Box 27, Folder 29)
- Staff Training 1199, 1965-1966 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- Course Material, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- Brooks 1968 Sabbatical (Box 27, Folder 32)
- Course Material, 1955-1967 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- To Bernie Flaherty, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Training Teachers Ind. Inventories, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Western Pulp-Paper '68 training in bargaining, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Consumers Power, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- ABC Paper Co. Case, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- New York Schools, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Course Material Severas operations, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Union Leaders, 1985-1986 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- CB Seminar 8/1-5/77, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 11)